<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<rss xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>ZenFocus</title>
        <item>
            <title>ZenFocus Changelogs</title>
            <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 17:01:29 +0545</pubDate>
            <sparkle:version>301</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>0.3.1</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>14.0</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <description><![CDATA[
                <h2>🎉 v0.3.1 New Features</h2>
                 <ul>
                <li><strong>Edit your tasks </strong> - Now you can edit tasks, add category, and due date directly from the editing view. </li>
                    <li><strong>Start your focus session directly</strong> - Brought back the feature to start a focus session directly. </li>
                <li><strong>Removed focus start animation</strong> - Now, you can configure whether you want to see the focus start animation or not via the settings. </li>
                <li><strong>Focuse session break</strong> - Go into break mode even without completing the task. Just press the pause button in the mini task view. </li>
                <li><strong>Join Discord</strong> - To get a full overview of changes, join our discord community from the settings. </li>
                </ul>
                
                
                
                
                <h2>🎉 v0.3.0 New Features</h2>
                 <ul>
                    <li><strong>Add Scheduled date to tasks!</strong> - Add scheduled dates to your tasks using @ as a trigger. </li>
                <li><strong>Add Category</strong> - Instead of using @ for category, use # now(since @ is used for scheduled date. </li>
                <li><strong>Removed direct focus start session</strong> - Now you have to properly plan your day and prioritize your tasks in order to start a focus session. </li>
                </ul>
                
                <h2>🎉 v0.2.9 New Features</h2>
                <ul>
                    <li><strong>Two-Level Hierarchy Support!</strong> - Organize your tasks with enhanced structure using our new two-level hierarchy system.</li>
                <li><strong>Better Stats View</strong> - Supports stats for both parent and child categories for better overview of where your time is being spent. </li>
                </ul>

                <h3>⚠️ Important Migration Note</h3>
                <p>To take advantage of the new hierarchy feature, you'll need to migrate your existing data to the new format. The app will guide you through this process during the first launch.</p>

                <h2>🛠️ Bug Fixes & Improvements</h2>
                <ul>
                    <li>Fixed stats view not updating properly</li>
                    <li>Resolved inconsistencies in completed task history view</li>
                    <li>Enhanced task editing stability and consistency</li>
                </ul>

                <h2>🤝 Community & Feedback</h2>
                <p>Join our growing community! Share your thoughts, get insights on upcoming features, or suggest improvements in our <a href="https://discord.gg/bJUxA9EV">Discord channel</a>.</p>

        
            ]]></description>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/Beingpax/ZenFocus-App/releases/download/v0.3.1/ZenFocus.dmg" length="4977992" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:edSignature="VZ/ANGj9IaCb+2sd9G2xsLmhejKVOTDMpw75XD9qOY1H3bd34lF5gl1uvtxmi7vkvemQg8zHuqZofvy+N3xoBA=="/>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
